Guide to the Sam di Bonaventura papers, 1900-1998
George Mason University Libraries
- Dr. Sam di Bonaventura papers
  - Mozart Concerto: Wind [1962-1976] (Box 76)
    Content: Notes, ARticles Headings: 1.Bassoon, 2.Cello (EMPTY), 3.Clarinet, 4.Concertone, 5.Flute No. 1, 6.Flute No. 2, 7.Flute-Harp, 8.Horn No. I, 9.Horn No. 2, 10.Horn No. 3 (EMPTY), 11.Horn No. 4, 12.Misc., 13.Oboe Dates of materials: 1962-1976
  - Mozart Concerto: Strings [1952-1959] (Box 77)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Violin No. 1, 2.Violin No. 2 (EMPTY), 3.Violin No. 3, 4.Violin No. 4, 5.Violin No. 5, 6.Sinfonia Concertante Dates of materials: 1952-1959
  - Mozart Opera I [1961-1979] (Box 77)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Apollo, 2.Ascanio, 3.Bastien, 4.Clemenza di Tito, 5.Cosi Fan Tutte Dates of materials: 1961-1979
  - Mozart Opera II [1964-1982] (Box 77)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Don Giovanni, 2.Entfuring [aus dem Serail], 3.Finta Giardiniera, 4.Finta Semplice, 5.Idomeneo, 6.Lucio Silla, 7.Misc. Dates of materials: 1964-1982
  - Mozart Opera III [1965-1986] (Box 77)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Mitridate, 2.Nozze di Figaro, 3.Oca del Cairo, 4.Re Pastore, 5.Schaispieldirektor, 6.Schuldigkeit, 7.Sogno, 8.Sposo Delusso, 9.Thamos, 10.Zaide, 11.Zauberflote Dates of materials: 1965-1986
  - Mozart Symphony [1965-1981] (Box 78)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Misc., 2.Nos. 1-9, 3.Nos. 10-19 (EMPTY), 4.Nos. 20-29, 5.Nos. 30-34, 6.Unlabeled (No. 35), 7.No. 36, 8.No. 37 (EMPTY), 9.No. 38, 10.No. 39, 11.Unlabeled (No. 40), 12.No. 41 Dates of materials: 1965-1981
  - Mudarra 1993 (Box 78)
    Content: Scholarly Paper, Musical Scores, Bibliography Headings: 1.None (Scholarly Papter), 2.Realizations, 3.Computer Literals, 4.Unlabeled (Fantasia, Bk 1, Fol. 1), 5.Original Manuscript Dates of materials: 1993
  - Music Definitions 1976 (Box 78)
    Content: Notes, Musical Scores, Illustrations Headings: 1.Melody, 2.Harmony, 3.Tonality, 4.Rhythm, 5.Meter, 6.Dynamics, 7.Texture, 8.Form Dates of materials: 1976
  - Music History I 1969 (Box 78)
    Content: Articles Headings: None (History; Music History)- fills one 1" binder Dates of materials: 1969
  - Music History II 1994 (Box 78)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Unlabeled (Discussion premise), 2.(Midieval), 3.(Renaissance: Art), 4.(Baroque), 5.(Classical), 6.(Romantic), 7.(20th Century), 8.Notation Dates of materials: 1994
  - Music History III (Box 79)
    Content: Notes, ARticles Headings: 1.Beginning, 2.Medieval, 3.Renaissance, 4.Baroque, 5.Classical, 6.Romantic Dates of materials: ?
  - Mussorgsky [1946-1984] (Box 79)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Concert Programs, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Bibliography (EMPTY), 2.Biography, 3.Choral Misc., 4.Complete Works (EMPTY), 5.Misc., 6.Opera, 7.Piano Misc., 8.Song, 9.Style, 10.Tone Poem Dates of materials: 1946-1984
  - Nielson [1959-1985] (Box 79)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Bibliography (EMTPY), 2.Biography, 3.Cantata (EMPTY), 4.Chamber Misc., 5.Choral Misc. (EMPTY), 6.Concerto, 7.Fantasia, 8.Hymn (EMPTY), 9.Incid. Music (EMPTY), 10.Instr. Misc. (EMPTY), 11.Letters (EMPTY), 12.Literary (EMPTY), 13.Misc., 14.Motet (EMPTY), 15.Opera, 16.Orch. Misc. (EMPTY), 17.Organ Misc., 18.Overture (EMPTY), 19.Piano Misc. (EMPTY), 20.Prelude (EMPTY), 21.Quartet (EMPTY), 22.Quintet, 23.Rhapsody (EMPTY), 24.Serenade (EMPTY), 25.Sonata (EMPTY), 26.Song (EMPTY), 27.Song Cycle (EMPTY), 28.Style, 29.Suite, 30.Symphony, 31.Trio (EMPTY), 32.Variation (EMPTY) Dates of materials: 1959-1985
  - Obrecht/Ockeghem [1963-1968] (Box 79)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Obrecht, Jacob (1430-1505) (Complete works, Canzona, Mass, Motet), 2.Ockeghem, Johannes (1430-95) (Biography, Chanson, Mass, Motet) Dates of materials: 1963-1968
  - Offenbach/Orff [1961-1986] (Box 79)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Offenbach (Opera, Biography, Operetta, Offenbach, Ballet), 2.Orff (Pedgogical, Choral Misc., Cantata, Style; Biography) Dates of materials: 1961-1986
  - Opera 20th Cent. [1965-1969] (Box 80)
    Content: Articles, Concert Programs Headings: None (Fills 1.5" Binder) Dates of materials: 1965-1969
  - Opera A-L (Box 80)
    Content: Musical Scores Headings: 1.A, 2.B., 3.C, 4.D, 5.E (EMPTY), 6.F, 7.G, 8.H-J, 9.K, 10.L Dates of materials: ?
  - Opera M-O (Box 80)
    Content: Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.M, 2.N, 3.O Dates of materials: ?
  - Opera P-Z (Box 80)
    Content: Musical Scores Headings: 1.P-Q, 2.R, 3.S, 4.T, 5.U-V, 6.W, 7.X-Z Dates of materials:
  - Paganini [1959-1979] (Box 81)
    Content: Articles, Musical Scores Headings: None (Sonata, Variation, Concerto, Style, Paganini, Misc.) Dates of materials: 1959-1979
  - Palestrina (Box 81)
    Content: Notes, Musical Scores, Articles Headings: 1.None (Palestrina), 2.(Palestrina: Life), 3.(Ave Virgo/Ave, Gloriosa/Domino), 4.(Palestrina: Motet), 5.(Super Flumina Babylonis), 6.(Mass), 7.(Summary of 13th c. Motet), 8.(The Counter-Reformation), Dates of materials: ?
  - Palestrina/Persichetti [1964-1972] (Box 81)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Scholarly Papers, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Palestrina, Perluigi da (1526-94) (Motet, Mass, Complete Works, Lamentations, Missa Domenicali, Missa Ad Fugam, Missa Ut Re Mi Fa Sol La; Palestrina;, 2.Persichetti, Vince (Biograph, Symphony, Style, Sonata; Misc., Concerto, Serenade, Chamber Misc., Song, Misc., Orch. Misc., Vocal Misc., Complete Works, Band Music, Choral, Persichetti, Concerto, Pfte) Dates of materials: 1964-1972
  - Partch (Box 81)
    Content: Illustrations Headings: 1.Melody Instruments, 2.Percussion Instruments Dates of materials: ?
  - Penderecki [1968-1979] (Box 81)
    Content: Articles, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: None (Orch Misc, Magnificat, Choral Misc, Passion, Quartet, Stabat Mater, Concerto, Biography, Works, Oratorio, Quartet) Dates of materials: 1968-1979
  - Performance Practice I [1980-1983 (Box 81)
    Content: Articles Headings: 1.Performance Practice, 2.Medieval, 3.Renaissance, 4.Baroque, 5.Classical, 6.Romantic, 7.Modern Dates of materials: 1980-1983
  - Performance Practice II [1976-1981] (Box 82)
    Content: Notes, Articles Headings: 1.Misc., 2.Performance, 3.History Dates of materials: 1976-1981
  - Performers I [1966-1968] (Box 82)
    Content: Articles, Notes Headings: 1.Guitarists, 2.Harpists, 3.(Clavichordists: 20th C.), 4.(Organists: 20th C.), 5.(Bassoonists: 20th C.), 6.Clarinettists, 7.(Flutists: 20th C.), 8.Hornists, 9.Oboists, 10.Trumpeters, 11.Misc. Dates of materials: 1966-1968
  - Pergolesi [1968-1984] (Box 82)
    Content: Articles, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: None (Opera; Concertino; Concerto; Biography; Sonata; Sacred Misc.) Dates of materials: 1968-1984
  - Pianists A-J [1967-1968] (Box 82)
    Content: Articles, Scholarly Papers, Concert Programs Headings: A-J information about pianists Dates of materials: 1967-1968
  - Pianists K-Z [1965-1968] (Box 82)
    Content: Articles, Scholarly Papers, Concert Programs Headings: K-Z information about pianists Dates of materials: 1965-1968
  - Piston [1980-1987] (Box 83)
    Content: Articles, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: None (Literary, Style, Complete Works, Quartet, Quintet, Divertimento, Prelude, Symphony, Ballet, Biography, Concerto, Piston, Capriccio, Chamber Music) Dates of materials: 1980-1987
  - Pop Musicians and Classical Music (Box 83)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Charts, 2.Explanation, 3.Beginning, 4.Concerto, 5.Symphony, 6.Opera, 7.Keyboard, 8.Instrumental, 9.Misc. (EMPTY) Dates of materials: ?
  - Poulenc [1946-1984] (Box 83)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: None (Style, Complete Works, Concerto, Song Cycle, Sextet, Opera, Song, Toccata, Ballet, Motet, Style, Sonata, Biography, Chanson, Duo, Poulenc, Trio) Dates of materials: 1946-1984
  - Program Notes A-Ba [1968-1998] (Box 83)
    Content: Program Notes (by Dr. Bonaventura), Articles Headings: 1.A, 2.B, 3.Bach, 4.Barber, 5.Bartok Dates of materials: 1968-1998
  - Program Notes Bern-Bra [1971-1994] (Box 83)
    Content: Program Notes (by Dr. Bonaventura), Articles Headings: 1.Bernstein, 2.Bizet, 3.Bloch, 4.Boccherini, 5.Borodin, 6.Brahms Dates of materials: 1971-1994
  - Program Notes Bri-Co [1979-1997] (Box 84)
    Content: Notes, Program Notes (by Dr. Bonaventura), Articles Headings: 1.Britten, 2.Bruch, 3.Bruckner, 4.C, 5.Chausson, 6.Chopin, 7.Copland Dates of materials: 1979-1997
  - Program Notes D-Ez [1974-1998] (Box 84)
    Content: Program Notes (by Dr. Bonaventura), Articles Headings: 1.D, 2.Debussy, 3.Delius, 4.Dukas, 5.Dvorak, 6.E, 7.Elgar, 8.Enesco Dates of materials: 1974-1998
  - Program Notes Fa-G [1979-1998] (Box 84)
    Content: Notes, Program Notes (by Dr. Bonaventura), Articles Headings: 1.F, 2.Falla, 3.Franck, 4.G, 5.Gershwin, 6.Ginastera, 7.Glazunov, 8.Glinka, 9.Gluck, 10.Gounod, 11.Grieg Dates of materials: 1979-1998
  - Program Notes H [1964-1998] (Box 84)
    Content: Notes, Program Notes (by Dr. Bonaventura), Articles Headings: 1.H, 2.Handel, 3.Haydn, 4.Hindemith, 5.Honegger, 6.Husa Dates of materials: 1964-1998
  - Program Notes I-Ma [1968-1997] (Box 85)
    Content: Notes, Program Notes (by Dr. Bonaventura), Articles Headings: 1.I, 2.Ibert, 3.D'Indy, 4.Ives, 5.J, 6.Unlabeled (K), 7.Khatchaturian, 8.Kodaly, 9.Krenek, 10.L, 11.Lalo, 12.Lees, 13.Lewis, 14.Liszt, 15.Lutoslawski, 16.M, 17.MacDowell, 18.Mahler, 19.Martinu Dates of materials: 1968-1997
  - Prokofiev Concerto [1968-1977] (Box 85)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Cello I, 2.Cello II, 3.Piano I, 4.Piano II, 5.Piano III, 6.Piano IV, 7.Piano V, 8.Violin I, 9.Violin II, 10.Misc. Dates of materials: 1968-1977
  - Prokofiev I [1947-1978] (Box 85)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Ballet, 2.Bibliography (EMPTY), 3.Biography, 4.Cantata, 5.Chamber Music, 6.Choralk Misc. (EMPTY), 7.Complete Works, 8.Dance (EMPTY), 9.Divirtimento (EMPTY), 10.Etude (EMPTY), 11.Film Music, 12.Incid. Music (EMPTY), 13.Instr. Misc. (EMPTY), 14.Letters (EMPTY), 15.Literary (EMPTY), 16.March (EMPTY), 17.Misc., 18.Ode (EMPTY), 19.Opera, 20.Orchestral Misc., 21.Overture (EMPTY), 22.Piano Misc., 23.Quartet Dates of materials: 1947-1978
  - Prokofiev II [1964-1969] (Box 85)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Quintet, 2.Sinfonietta (EMPTY), 3.Sonata, 4.Song (EMPTY), 5.Style, 6.Suite, 7.Symphony, 8.Toccata (EMPTY), 9.Tone Poem (EMPTY) Dates of materials: 1964- 1969
  - Puccini Opera I [1970-1980] (Box 86)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Bibliography, 2.Biography, 3.Capriccio (EMPTY), 4.Chamb. Misc (EMPTY), 5.Complete Works, 6.Hymn (EMPTY), 7.Instr. Misc (EMPTY), 8.Letters, 9.Mass, 10.Misc., 11.Orch. Misc, 12.Angelica (EMPTY), 13.Boheme, La, 14.Butterfly, 15.Edgar Dates of materials: 1970-1980
  - Puccini Opera II [1967-1984] (Box 86)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Fanciulla, 2.Manon Lescaut, 3.Misc., 4.Rondine, La, 5.Schicchi, 6.Tabarro, Il, 7.Tosca, 8.Trittico, 9.Turandot, 10.Villi, Le Dates of materials: 1967- 1984
  - Purcell [1973-1979] (Box 86)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: None (Opera; Style; Church Music; Theater Music; Biography; Ode; Collected Works; Misc.; Fantasia; Overture; Chaconne; Suite; Anthem; Lute Song; Round; Chamber Music; Purcell; Motet; Biography; Incid. Music; Song; Recordings; Sonata; Sacred Misc.; Variation; Dance) Dates of materials: 1973-1979
  - Rachmaninoff I [1976-1981] (Box 86)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Scholarly Papers, Concert Programs, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Bibliography (EMPTY), 2.Biography, 3.Capriccio, 4.Chamber Misc. (EMPTY), 5.Choral Misc., 6.Complete Works, 7.Concerto Dates of materials: 1976-1981
  - Rachmaninoff II [1946-1984] (Box 87)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Scholarly Papers, Concert Programs, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Dance, 2.Etude, 3.Fantasia, 4.Instrumental. Misc., 5.Letters (EMPTY), 6.Literary (EMPTY), 7.Mass (EMPTY), 8.Misc., 9.Opera, 10.Orchestral Misc. (EMPTY), 11.Piano Misc., 12.Prelude, 13.Rhapsody, 14.Sacred Misc., 15.Sonata, 16.Song, 17.Style, 18.Suite, 19.Symphony, 20.Tone Poem, 21.Transcription, 22.Variation Dates of materials: 1946-1984
  - Rameau/Reger [1960-1982] (Box 87)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Scholarly Papers, Concert Programs, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Reger (Style; Reger; Variation; Importance; Fugue; Organ Music; Passacaglia; Fantasia; Choral Prelude; Suite; Chamber Music; Sonata; Quintet; Quartet; Trio; Serenade; Biography; Catalogue of Works; Concerto; Piano Misc.; Life and Works; Requiem; Transcription; Psalm; Song; Choral Misc.), 2.Rameau, Jean Paul (1683-1764) (Opera; Keyboard Misc.; Misc.; Ballet; Harpsichord Misc.; Dance; Theoretical; Hymn; Suite; Cantata; Summary) Dates of materials: 1960-1982
  - Ravel I [1975-1984] (Box 87)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Scholarly Papers, Concert Programs, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Ballet, 2.Biography, 3.Chamber Music, 4.Complete Works, 5.Concerto Dates of materials: 1975-1984
  - Ravel II [1982-1984] (Box 87)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Scholarly Papers, Concert Programs, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Dance, 2.Instrumental Misc., 3.Unlabeled (Literary), 4.Misc., 5.Opera Dates of materials: 1982-1984
  - Ravel III [1953-1982] (Box 88)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Scholarly Papers, Concert Programs, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Orchestral Misc., 2.Piano Misc., 3.Quartet, 4.Rhapsody, 5.Sonata, 6.Song, 7.Unlabeled (Style), 8.Suite, 9.Unlabeled (Trio) Dates of materials: 1953-1982
  - Renaissance I 1957 (Box 88)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Humanism, 2.Canti Carnas., 3.Carol, 4.English School: I Dates of materials: 1957
  - Renaissance 2 1951 (Box 88)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Postcards, Class Notes Headings: 1.Misc., 2.General, 3.England, 4.France, 5.Spain, 6.Florence, 7.Mantua, 8.Ferrara, 9.Germany, 10.Burgundy, 11.Chanson, 12.Madrigal Dates of materials: 1951
  - Renaissance 3 1957 (Box 88)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.English, 2.Special, 3.Misc. Dates of materials: 1957
  - Renaissance VI (Box 89)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Notation, 2.Compositional Practice, 3.Germany (EMPTY), 4.Instrumental, 5.Secular Misc., 6.Canzone I Dates of materials: ?
  - Renaissance VII (Box 89)
    Content: Notes, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Mass: I, 2.Mass: II Dates of materials: ?
  - Respghi [1966-1985] (Box 89)
    Content: Notes, Articles Headings: 1.Unlabeled (Ballet), 2.(Biography), 3.(Cantata), 4.(Choral Misc.), 5.(Complete Works), 6.(Ode), 7.(Opera), 8.(Song), 9.(Style), 10.(Suite), 11.(Transcription) Dates of materials: 1966-1985
  - Riegger 1973 (Box 89)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Scholarly Papers Headings: None (Complete Works; Orch. Misc; Biography and Analysis of Selected Works; Instrumental Misc.; Ballet; Symphony; Style; Biography; Fantasia; Suite; Riegger) Dates of materials: 1973
  - Rimsky/Roussel [1967-1982] (Box 89)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Scholarly Papers, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Rimsky-Korsakoff, N. (1844-1908) (Capriccio; Suite; Opera, Tone Poem; Overture; Song; Style; Rimsky-Korsakoff; Chamber Music; Orchestral Misc.; Biography; Misc.), 2.(Roussel, Albert) (Catalogue of Works; Style; Ballet; Flute Misc.; Symphony; Suite; Roussel; Chamber Music; Ballet Suite; Life and Works) Dates of materials: 1967- 1982
  - Rochberg/Roman/Rorem [1965-1986] (Box 90)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Rochberg (Quartet; Song Cycle; Symphony; Harp Misc.; Quintet; Concerto; Song; Style; Orchestral Misc.; Chamber Misc.; Biography; Instr. Misc; Rochberg; Serenade; Biography; Complete Works), 2.Roman (Life and Catalogue of Works), 3.Rorem (Oratorio; Etude; Vocal Misc.; Harp Misc.; Instr. Misc.; Orch. Misc.; Concerto; Piano Concerto; Song; Symphony; Chamb. Misc.; Opera; Trio; Song Cycle; Rorem; Variation; Concerto; Literary) Dates of materials: 1965-1986
  - Rossini [1963-1983] (Box 90)
    Content: Notes, Articles Headings: 1.Bibliography, 2.Biography, 3.Cantata (EMPTY), 4.Choral Misc. (EMPTY), 5.Complete Wks, 6.Dance (EMPTY), 7.Incid. Mus. (EMPTY), 8.Letters (EMPTY), 9.March (EMPTY), 10.Mass, 11.Misc., 12.Piano Misc., 13.Quartet, 14.Sacred Misc. (EMPTY), 15.Serenade, 16.Sinfonia (EMPTY), 17.Sontata, 18.Stabat Mater, 19.Style, 20.Suite, 21.Variation, 22.Vocal Misc. Dates of materials: 1963-1983
  - Saint-Saens [1953-1981] (Box 90)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Bibliography (EMPTY), 2.Biography, 3.Cantata (EMPTY), 4.Capriccio (EMPTY), 5.Chamber Misc., 6.Choral Misc. (EMPTY), 7.Complete Wks., 8.Concerto, 9.Dance, 10.Duet (EMPTY), 11.Etude (EMPTY), 12.Fantasia (EMPTY), 13.Fugue (EMPTY), 14.Hymn (EMPTY), 15.Incid. Mus. (EMPTY), 16.Instr. Misc., 17.Letters (EMPTY), 18.Literary, 19.March (EMPTY), 20.Mass, 21.Misc., 22.Opera, 23.Oratorio, 24.Organ Misc. (EMPTY), 25.Overture (EMPTY), 26.Piano Misc., 27.Prelude (EMPTY), 28.Psalm (EMPTY), 29.Quartet (EMPTY), 30.Quintet (EMPTY), 31.Rhapsody (EMPTY), 32.Septet (EMPTY), 33.Serenade, 34.Sonata, 35.Song, 36.Style, 37.Suite, 38.Symphony, 39.Tone Poem, 40.Trio (EMPTY), 41.Variation (EMPTY) Dates of materials: 1953-1981
  - Satie I [1963-1968] (Box 90)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: None (Piano Misc.; Satie; Works; Style; Piano Music; Biography; Vexations; Rollo H. Myers: Erik Satie) Dates of materials: 1963-1968
  - Satie II (Box 90)
    Content: Xeroxes of musical score Headings: "Sports & Divertissements" by Satie Dates of materials: ? (1914)
  - Scarlatti [1972-1985] (Box 91)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Scarlatti, Alessandro (1659-1725), (Exultate Deo; Sonata; Cantata; Aria; Instrumental; Dance; Opera; Toccata; Mass; Motet; Sinfonia; Overture; Concerto), 2. Scarlatti, Domenico (1685-1757) (Biography; Sonata; Style; Sinfonia; Complete Works) Dates of materials: 1972-1985
  - Scheidt/Schein/Schuetz [1966-1972] (Box 91)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Scheidt, Samuel, (Mass; Tabulatura Nova; Bicinium; Canzona; Chorale; Variation; Chorale Prelude; Complete Works; Missa Dominicale; Fantasia; Samuel Scheidt), 2.(Schein, JH), (Gelobet seist du, Jesu Christ; Complete Works; Style; Chorale Concerto; Chorale; Concerto Literature; Concerto; Johann Hermann Schein: Songwriter), 3.Schuetz, Heinrich (1585-1672) (Psalm; Choral Misc.; Biography; Magnificat; Oratorio; Motet; Schuetz; Misc.; Concerto; Sacred. Misc.; Complete Works; Ballet; Requiem; Passion; Lied; Chorale) Dates of materials: 1966-1972
  - Schoenberg I [1961-1976] (Box 91)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Bibiolgraphy (EMPTY), 2.Biography, 3.Chamber Misc., 4.Choral Misc., 5.Complete Works, 6.Concerto, 7.Fantasia, 8.Letters, 9.Literary, 10.Misc., 11.Monodrama, 12.Opera, 13.Oratorio, 14.Orch. Misc., 15.Piano Misc. Dates of materials: 1961-76
  - Schoenberg II [1960-1982] (Box 91)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Prelude, 2.Quartet, 3.Quintet, 4.Sacred Misc., 5.Serenade, 6.Sextet, 7.Song, 8.Style, 9.Suite, 10.Symphony, 11.Theoretical, 12.Tone Poem, 13.Transcription, 14.Trio, 15.Variation Dates of materials: 1960-1982
  - Schubert I [1949-1981] (Box 92)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Bibliography, 2.Biography, 3.Cantata, 4.Chamb. Misc., 5.Choral Misc., 6.Comp. Wks, 7.Dance, 8.Fantasia, 9.Hymn, 10.Impromptu, 11.Incid, Music, 12.Instr. Misc. (EMPTY), 13.Letters (EMPTY), 14.Magnificat, 15.Mass Dates of materials: 1949-1981
  - Schubert II [1966-1982] (Box 92)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Misc, 2.Octet, 3.Opera, 4.Orch. Misc. (EMPTY), 5.Overture (EMPTY), 6.Piano Misc., 7.Psalm (EMPTY), 8.Quartet, 9.Quintet, 10.Rondo, 11.Salve Regina (EMPTY), 12.Sonata, 13.Sonatina (EMPTY), 14.Song, 15.Stabat Mater (EMPTY), 16.Style, 17.Trio, 18.Variation Dates of materials: 1966-1982
  - Schubert Song (Box 92)
    Content: Notes, Musical Scores Headings: 1.X (An die Musik), 2.XI (Wohin), 3.XVII (Lied der Mignon) Dates of materials: ?
  - Schubert Symphony [1971-1982] (Box 92)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Misc., 2.No.1, 3.No. 2, 4.No. 3, 5.No. 4, 6.No. 5, 7.No. 6, 8.No. 7, 9.No. 8, 10.(No. 9) Dates of materials: 1971-1982
  - Schuller/Schuman/Sessions [1967-1981] (Box 92)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Schuller, Gunther (1925-) (Schuller; Invention; Orch. Misc.; Sonata; Literary; Biography; Overture; Symphony; Style; Biography; Etude; Tone Poem; Opera; Quartet; Concerto; Misc.; Complete Works; Seven Studies on Themes of Paul Klee), 2.Schuman, William (1910-) (Biography; Style; Complete Works; Concerto; Literary; Misc.; Orch. Misc.; Instr. Misc; Transcription; Ballet; Symphony; Overture; Variationl Aesthetics; Opera; Schuman; Vocal Misc.), 3.Sessions, Roger (1896-) (Sonata; Quartet; Rhapsody; Symphony; Works; Misc.; Cantata; Biography; Sessions; Concertino; Aesthetics; Incid. Mus.; Style; Concertp; Opera; Vocal Misc.) Dates of materials: 1967-1981
  - Schumann [1964-1982] (Box 93)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Biography, 2.Chamber Misc., 3.Choral Misc., 4.Complete Works, 5.Concerto, 6.Incid. Music, 7.Instr. Misc., 8.Letters, 9.Literary, 10.(Mass), 11.Misc., 12.Opera, 13.Oratorio, 14.Orch, Misc., 15.Overture, 16.Piano Misc., 17.Quartet, 18.Quintet, 19.Sacred Misc. (EMPTY), 20.Sonata, 21.Song, 22.Style, 23.Suite, 24.Trio, 25.Variation Dates of materials: 1964-1982
  - Schumann Symphony [1973-1976] (Box 93)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Symphony Misc., 2.No.1, 3.No. 2, 4.No. 3, 5.No. 4 Dates of materials: 1973-1976
  - Scriabin/Sullivan/Sweelinck [1968-1976] (Box 93)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Scriabin (Etude; Prelude; Piano Misc.; Sonata; Orch. Misc.; Piano Music; Symphony; Scriabin; Biography; Style; Tone Poem; Fantasia; Keyboard), 2.Sullivan (Operetta; Sullivan; Misc.; Song), 3.Sweelinck, Jan P (1562-1621) (Ricercar; Complete Works; Harpsichord Misc.; Bicinium; Fantasia; Organ Misc.; Psalm; Motet; Variations) Dates of materials: 1968-1976
  - Shakes[peare] 1996 (Box 93)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Misc., 2.Elson Masters, 3.Elson, 4.Hartnoll Dates of materials: 1996
  - Shostakovich I [1967-1981] (Box 94)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Ballet, 2.Bibliography (EMPTY), 3.Biography, 4.Cantata, 5.Choral Misc., 6.Complete Works, 7.(Concerto), 8.Dance, 9.Film Music, 10.Incid. Music (EMTPY), 11.Instr. Misc. (EMPTY), 12.Letters (EMPTY), 13.Literary, 14.Misc., 15.Octet (EMPTY), 16.Opera, 17.Orch, Misc., 18.Overture (EMPTY), 19.Piano Misc. (EMPTY) Dates of materials: 1967-1981
  - Shostakovich II [1962-1982] (Box 94)